承诺，我们对承诺有什么了解 ?
Promises, what do we know about promises?
我有一个很好的报价，我从 MDN 那里偷来的，我最喜欢的网站。
I actually have a good quote that I
stole from MDN, my favorite website.
我引述的是甚么 ?
What is my quote?
我们对承诺有什么了解 ?
What do we know about promises?
有人告诉我
Someone tell me something.
>> 将返回的将返回的值。
&gt;&gt; Someting that will
return with a future value.
> > 嗯，我喜欢
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I like that.
我将使用 MDN 定义，因为它比我能说的更好得多。
I'll use the MDN definition because it's
much better than anything I can say.
我可以说一个承诺就是
I can say a promise is a proxy for
在创建承诺时不一定知道的值。
value that's not necessarily known
when the promise is created.
一个承诺就是，就是这样，
Which a promise is, it's exactly that,
最终会有回报的
it's a promise to return
something eventually.
你不知道
You don't know what.
你不知道什么时候或者什么时候但你知道最终会发生什么
You don't know where or when, but
you know what happens eventually, so
我们在这附近进行计划
we program around that.
旧的处理价值，我们不知道它会是什么，但是
The old style of handling values that
we don't know what it's gonna be, but
我们知道我们想让它最终回到旧学的回调
we know we want it to return eventually
would be using old school callbacks.
因此，在回调函数中调用函数时，它会执行某些工作，然后
So in a callback you invoke a function,
it does some work and then whenever it's
完成后，它会调用函数以传递该值或执行任何您想做的操作。
done, it calls back the function to pass
on that value or do whatever you wanna do.
随着承诺的发明，我们现在可以将事物联系在一起，
With the invention of promises,
we can now chain things together and
我不必每次都显式地调用回调。
I don't have to explicitly call
the callback every single time.
我们可以把它链起来
We can just chain this together.
希望在这个阶段的 JavaScript 工程中
Hopefully, not hopefully,
at this stage in JavaScript engineering or
你应该知道什么是什么承诺。
UI engineering you should
probably know what promises are.
你以更清洁的方式了解他们，就像异步等待一样。
You know them in a much
cleaner way as async await.
但你仍然需要承诺，你仍然需要了解他们的工作方式
But you still need promises, you still
need to understand how they work because
许多代码，尤其是旧节点库，它们不使用异步等待。
a lot of code, especially old node
libraries, they don't use async await.
它们使用回调。
They use callbacks.
因此，您需要了解如何履行承诺，履行承诺，并且
So you need to know how promises work
to wrap a callback with a promise and
那就回去吧
then return that.
异步等待很漂亮
Async await is pretty.
这是一个很漂亮的语法。
It's a much prettier syntax.
如果你不能告诉你你只能等待一些事情
If you can't tell,
you can just await something and
最终它会为您提供该值与回调。
eventually it gives you
that value versus callback.
你见过多姆的飞行 V 吗
And then you ever seen
the Flying V of doom?
在您具有回调和回调和回调的位置，因为这将是回调，
Where you have callbacks and callbacks and
callbacks because this will be a callback,
这将是回调，这将是您的回调。
and this will be a callback and
this will be your callback.
Async 等待解决所有这些问题。
Async await solves all of that.
多漂亮的人
Much prettier.
所以我有两个问题，我们还有两个问题。
So I have two questions,
we have two questions left.
我不会给你一个承诺的
And I won't give you a promise phi one.
我要把它放在 advanced 节里
I'll leave that in the advanced section.
所以我有一个问题是原来的，更难的问题是，
So I have one question, which
the original, the harder question is,
给一个这样的一个功能，我怎么把这个转化为一个承诺呢 ?
given a function that looks like this,
how would I convert that into a promise?
我把它递给我然后把它转换成一个承诺
I pass this and
then convert it to a promise,
这比你想象的更具挑战性
it's more challenging than you think.
给它一次机会，答案当然在答案部分，
Give it a shot sometime, the answers
are of course in the answer section,
但我们会做一个较短的睡眠功能
but we'll do a shorter one,
sleep function.
现在，如果我说的是 JavaScript ，你在想什么呢 ?
Now implicitly if I say sleep to
the JavaScript, what are you thinking?
>> 线程休眠。
&gt;&gt; Thread sleep.
>> 是，但我们能用 JavaScript 来做吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Yeah, but can we do that in JavaScript?
不我们不能去
No, we can't.
没错你会喜欢的 Gem 你这个帅哥
Exactly, you'd be like,
Gem, you handsome fool.
你不能用 JavaScript 来睡眠它是单线程的它运行和运行
You can't sleep in JavaScript, it'
single threaded, it just runs and runs,
停止线程的最佳方式是无限循环。
the best you can do to stop
a thread would be an infinite loop.
然后就把整个东西都锁起来了
And then it just locks
up the entire thing.
所以我们不一定要睡在主线里，但我可以在一个功能上睡觉。
So we can't necessarily sleep in the main
thread, but I can sleep in a function.
在等待什么的同时
As in using await or something along
我可以使此函数在此处等待指定的时间间隔，并且
those lines I can make this function wait
here for a specified interval of time and
调整功能，我不能在全局范围上做，什么都做不到。
adjust a function, I couldn't do this on
the global scope or anything like that.
所以用这个，这是最后一个问题。
So using this, this is the last problem.
创建一个以一个参数为时间的睡眠功能，并且
Create a sleep function that takes
one parameter, which is time, and
我们将等待时间
we'll wait time milliseconds.
我甚至给你举个例子
I even graciously gave you an example,
而你却不可能真正的生活
which you would not get
in real life probably.
那就睡了 500 毫秒后它就会打印好
So sleep, it's gonna wait 500 milliseconds
then it's gonna print hello and
然后再等五百毫秒打个招呼
then it's gonna wait 500 milliseconds and
print hello.
我给你十分钟的时间
And I'll give you ten minutes on this one.
这是你最后一天的最后一个问题
This is the last problem for
the day then you've made it.
希望我能模拟真实生活耗尽你会得到的
And hopefully I've simulated real life
exhaustion that you'd get [LAUGH] in
一个战术面试
a tactical interview.